## YONGJIN HAN

5109, 30, Pildong-ro 1-gil, Jung-gu, Seoul, Republic of Korea (+82) 10-2966-1804 # yj94730@gmail.com

### Summary

I am interested in program verification, program synthesis and program analysis for reliable and secure software. Also, I conducted several projects that I have worked on as a research assistant, including two projects sponsored by the National Research Foundation of Korea.

#### **Education**

B.E. in Computer Science and Engineering, Dongguk University.

02/2021

Gap year from summer 2017 to spring 2019 due to military service.

#### License

Industrial engineer information security in Korea in 2016

### Experience

### Research assistant, Programming Language and Secure Software lab in Dongguk University 07/2019 - Present

Researching on compiler including VM interpreter and secure software

#### **President, Computer Security Club in Dongguk University**

03/2020 - 02/2021

Leading a security group focusing on system hacking, pwnable.

#### CERT (Computer Emergency Response Team), Republic of Korea Army 08/2017 - 05/2019

Monitoring traffic, intrusion detection logs such as DDOS, spoofing, and viruses Dealing with computer emergent accidents

Auditing other soldiers from staff sergeant to lieutenant colonel whether they consistently comply with security rules or not.

## **Research and Project**

(Project sponsored by <u>the National Research Foundation of Korea</u>) Development of the Distributed Virtual Machine and the Intelligence Offloading Method for A Smart Edge Computing 03/2020 - 02/2021

- Developing VM interpreter
- Optimizing VM interpreter with lazy evaluation

## (Project sponsored by <u>the National Research Foundation of Korea</u>) Smart Community Policing system 03/2020 - 02/2021

- Developing predictive policing system with ETAS (Epidemic Type Aftershock Sequence) model and machine learning
- Designing crime magnitude scoring model to convert crime events to earthquake events

## (Research) Reduction in test case to evaluate and improve performance of static analyzer 03/2020 - 02/2021

- Analyzing how released static analyzers detect vulnerabilities
- Implementation a tool to find vulnerable codes area using data flow analysis with LLVM

## (Student project) Automated Debugging with Program Synthesis and Fault Localization 03/2020 - 12/2020

- Team leader of the project
- Designing a whole process of the automated debugger
- Implementation program synthesizer to correct selected bug code

# (Project) Developing self-educating system about secure software in web application 01/2020 - 02/2020

- Implementation backend as REST API using Django to handle requests from user transactions

# (Student Research) A Research on weakness analysis technique based on SMT solver 09/2019 - 12/2019

- Implementation integer buffer overflow analyzer using z3, SMT solver

### **Presentation and Paper**

Yongjin Han, Soo-Lyn Choi, Sun-Young Ihm, and Yunsik Son, "A Predictive Policing with Epidemic Type Aftershock Sequence Model," In Proceedings of the 2nd International Conference on SMART Policing Convergence, Seoul, Oct 22, 2020.

Yongjin Han, Soo-Lyn Choi, JoongYeon Lim, Sun-Young Ihm. "A Research on the Prediction of Outside Accident of the Troops based on Earthquake Analysis Model." Korean Journal of Military Art and Science. Vol 76.3. pp 119-144. 2020.

Yongjin Han, Seokmin Chang, Yunsik Son. "A Study on the Virtual Machine Performance Optimization Using Lazy Evaluation." Korea Multimedia Society Conference. Aug 11, 2020.

## **Teaching Experience**

Class Tutor, Compiler Construction 09/2020 - 12/2020
Class Tutor, Programming Language and Theory 09/2020 - 12/2020

## Award and Scholarship

Senior scholarship in Introduction to the Capstone Design Course 1, 2020

Best Paper, Summer Conference by Korea Multi Media Society, Korea Federation of Information Technology Societies, 2020

A silver prize, Programming Contest, Dongguk University, 2017

A bronze prize, Programming Contest, Dept of CSE, Dongguk University, 2016